Guide to the George B. Post Architectural Records circa 1860–1997 (bulk, 1880–1980) PR 53
New-York Historical Society
- Series VI. 2002 Accrual, 1894-1997; 354 Linear feet in 147 boxes.
  - Subseries VI.F. Rolled Drawings, 1936-1993; 291 Linear feet in 83 boxes.
    - 70-1620 | Nissequogue Golf Club (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-570)
    - 70-1621 | All Sparrow Work (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-517)
    - 70-1622 | Thomas Peters VA. 1970-71-71 Job (from Box 6 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-508)
    - 70-1624 | Addition to J. Hadley Summer Home (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-510)
    - H70-1625-A | Bank of Smithtown (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-512)
    - H70-1625-B | Bank of Smithtown Kings Park | [Negatives removed and sealed awaiting further packing] (from Box 4 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-538)
    - H70-1625-B | [Mylar Negatives removed from] Bank of Smithtown Kings Park [now stored in 1 0170 00000 6774] (from Box 4 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-541)
    - H70-1625-C | [Bank of Smithtown Lake, Grove] (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-501)
    - H70-1625-C | Bank of Smithtown Lake Grove Branch "as filed" record copies (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-512)
    - 70-1627 | Crossman - Pratt (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-510)
    - 70-1629 | Additions to Allan [I.] Berkowitz (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-514)
    - 70-1630 | Hoguet (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-516)
    - 70-1632 | Dr. W. C. Porter Add. and Alt. to Res. (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-511)
    - 70-1633 | Storment Res. (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-517)
    - 70-1634 | Doeller (from Box 6 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-523)
    - 70-1636 | WGSM Radio (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-509)
    - 70-1642 | Hargrayes (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-501)
    - 70-1642 | Hargraves (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-509)
    - 70-1645 | Dudley Kit. Alt. (from Box 5 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-532)
    - 70-1646 | E. E. Post Jr New Vernon N.J. (from Box 8) (Offsite-box RD-516)
    - 71-1648 | Sweezey add. to store (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-501)
    - 71-1649 | Mitchell (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-501)
    - 71-1650 | Eastwoods (from Box 5 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-532)
    - 71-1650 | Eastwoods School (from Box 5 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-532)
    - 71-1650 | Eastwoods School (from Box 5 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-545)
    - 71-1651 | Stanton, [Mas] Addition and Alt. (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-502)
    - 71-1652 | Deutscher Alt. To Res. (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-510)
    - 71-1653 | Schwerin (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-511)
    - 71-1653 | Schwerin (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-512)
    - 71-1654 | Campbell Estate (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-577)
    - 71-1655 | Epis. Mission Soc. (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-511)
    - 71-1655 | Saint Barnabas (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-570)
    - 71-1655 | St. Barnabus (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-572)
    - 71-1655 | Warren Schwerin Res. (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-575)
    - 71-1656 | Olney Stable (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-502)
    - 71-1657 | Deming (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-502)
    - 71-1658 | Castle Assoc. (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-501)
    - 71-1660 | H. Ammidor Adds. and Alts. (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-502)
    - 71-1660 | Hoyt Ammidon J.R. (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-511)
    - 71-1661 | Martin (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-512)
    - 71-1662 | Cummings Pool (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-576)
    - 71-1674 | D. Kislak Prop. (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-502)
    - 71-1675 | Tomlinson Pool House (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-577)
    - 71-1676 | Half Hollow Hills School (from Box 5 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-526)
    - 71-1679 | Pope (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-565)
    - 71-1683 | Mr. and Mrs. Charles O. Ames Res. Additions and Alts. (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-502)
    - 71-1683 | Ames Residence (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-511)
    - 71-1683 [D and E] | Bank of Smithtown [maps for branch and haoppaoage branch] (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-511)
    - 71-1683 | Charles E. Ames Jr. Landscaping (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-570)
    - 71-1685 | Gerry (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-512)
    - 71-1686 | H. C. Taylor Residence (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-512)
    - 71-1687 | Morris Kaplan Residence (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-511)
    - 72-1294 | Parsons Sr. (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-520)
    - 72-1688 | Trow Bridge (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-577)
    - 72-1689 and 16- [cut off] | Gwydir Kra- [cut off] (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-575)
    - 72-1692 | Hamsley (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-577)
    - 72-1693 | Sunguam Sch. (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-575)
    - 72-1695 | [illegible] Robt. (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-575)
    - 72-1698 | Whalebone Landing Senne (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-576)
    - 72-1699 | [Prent] Brower (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-577)
    - 72-1700 | Brooks Harry (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-575)
    - 72-1701 | Gray Austen T. (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-575)
    - 72-1703 | Banks (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-520)
    - 72-1704 | Merritt (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-575)
    - 72-1705 | Amagansett Shopping Center (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-520)
    - 72-1706 | Lessard (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-576)
    - 72-1707 | Lealy (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-577)
    - 72-1708 | Frothyham (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-577)
    - 72-1712 | Dekay (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-577)
    - 72-1713 | Eggert, Joseph Jr. (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-577)
    - 72-1719 | Woolverton (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-577)
    - [72-1720] | [plus unlabeled jobs wrapped together] | [various jobs] (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-576)
    - 72-1724 | Spen[c/s]er (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-575)
    - 72-[1725] | Bartlett (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-577)
    - 72-1727 | Murray Laurel Hollow (from Box 9) (Offsite-box RD-510)
    - 72-1729 | East Woods School [Illegible] (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-577)
    - 72-1731 | Noyes (for B. U. Hall) (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-575)
    - 72-1732 | Mitchell Indust. Bldg. (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-577)
    - 72-1733 | Feinberg (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-575)
    - 72-1734 | T. [August] [illegible] (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-577)
    - 72-1735 | Dall (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-577)
    - 72-1739 | C. S. H. [Beach] Club (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-575)
    - 73-1743 | Mitchell [Mazda] (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-520)
    - 73-1744 | Lindley Miller (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-520)
    - 73-1745 | Horace Brock Res. One story addition 1975 with drawings for two story addition 1973-1745 | bought from [Henry] G Walter 2 story addition dwgs. 66-1482 | also M and A [isc] sketch | Struppman - prints of garage alts. | also Philip Wadsworth archt. Tracings for his original house (designed by him) (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-519)
    - 73-1747 | Bleeker (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-519)
    - 73-1748 | Dominicana Development (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-520)
    - 73-1749 | Andrade (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-521)
    - 73-1751 | Bacchiani (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-521)
    - 73-1752 | Hovey Misc Details on unnumbered sheets (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-522)
    - 73-1752 | Hovey Residence (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-522)
    - 73-1752 | Hovey (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-522)
    - 73-1753 | Grinell Morris Res. Center Island | Prints to [begins:] being sold to Chasmeyer (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-521)
    - 73-1758 | Williams (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-522)
    - 73-1760 | Hoguet (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-521)
    - 73-1761 | McCardy (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-519)
    - 73-1763 | [Robt] Loew Res. Fonda, NY (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-522)
    - 73-1764 | Irwin (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-521)
    - 73-1765 | DeKay (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-520)
    - 73-1767 | Chas. Brown (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-520)
    - 74-1770 | Radley (from Box 5 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-531)
    - 74-1771 | J. C. Miller Res. (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-522)
    - 74-1772 | Bachle (from Box 2 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-568)
    - 74-1773 | Details [Mesewe] Res. St. James (food with [drawing] of Morris Res May 25 94 73-1753) (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-522)
    - 74-1773 | Meserve (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-520)
    - 74-1774 | Paul (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-521)
    - 74-1777 | Kinney (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-520)
    - 74-1778 | Boone (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-520)
    - 74-1779 | Cushman (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-519)
    - 74-1781 | Mitchell (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-519)
    - 74-1783 | Horvath (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-521)
    - 74-1784 | Sam Post (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-520)
    - 74-1785 | Castle Assocs. (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-520)
    - [74-1786] | [Munroe] (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-521)
    - 74-1787 | Lamont (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-519)
    - 74-1788 | Seggerman, F. B. (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-519)
    - 74-1790 | Mariani - 1 (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-519)
    - 74-1796 | McRoberts (from Box 11) (Offsite-box RD-521)
    - 74-1947 | Visiting Nurse (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-530)
    - 75-1618 | Epis. Misson Soc. (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-560)
    - 75-1730 | Brown (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-576)
    - 75-1798 | Muller (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-560)
    - 75-1802 | Heurtley (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-559)
    - 75-1804 | T. R. Sanctuary Trailside Visitors Ctr. (from Box 5 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-550)
    - 75-1805 | Crimi, Michael J. (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-558)
    - 75-1809 | Little (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-558)
    - 75-1811 | Lindsay (E. A.) (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-549)
    - 75-1814 | Oak Tree Farm Dairy (from Box 5 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-531)
    - 75-1820 | Scheiwe Valley Road (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-559)
    - 75-1821 | Howard (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-559)
    - 75-1823 | [Schefren] (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-559)
    - 75-1824 | Nature Conservancy (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-559)
    - 75-1826 | Moon (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-549)
    - 75-1829 | Crocker (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-560)
    - 75-1832 | Pratt [Cem.] Plot (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-559)
    - 75-1833 | Palmer (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-549)
    - 75/76/77-[unknown job number] | Donald Brown (from Box 10) (Offsite-box RD-577)
    - 76-1835 | Whitman Village (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-558)
    - 76-1837 | Whitman (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-558)
    - 76-1838 | Gilmor (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-559)
    - 76-1839 | Shepardson (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-558)
    - 76-1840 | Dudley Porch - Sunroom Addition (from Box 5 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-526)
    - 76-1841 | Hewitt (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-559)
    - 76-1842 | Rosenberg (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-558)
    - 76-1844 | Pierson (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-549)
    - 76-1845 | Fates (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-560)
    - 76-1846 | Coleman Sr. (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-560)
    - 76-1847 | Coleman Jr. (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-558)
    - 76-1852 | Schland Res. (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-558)
    - 76-1848 | Bachelder (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-549)
    - 76-1853 | Bridgeman (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-559)
    - 76-1856 | Kassl (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-549)
    - 76-[1858] | W. O. Bannard (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-559)
    - 76-1860 | Cushman Seal Harbor (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-559)
    - 76-1862 | Bachelder - T. M. I. Bldg. (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-549)
    - 76-1864 | Klein (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-559)
    - 76-1866 | Lawrence (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-560)
    - 76-1868 | Adelphi Sch. of Nursing (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-558)
    - 76-1869 | Alarm Clock (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-559)
    - 76-186[?] | Hoppin pool house also house alt sketches 1976 and 83 (from Box 6) 66-1462 (Offsite-box RD-537)
    - 76-1870 | [Presbyterian] Church of Sweet Hollow (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-549)
    - 76-1870 | Pres. Church of Sweet Hollow (from Box 12) Also 83-2077 (Offsite-box RD-549)
    - 76-1873 | Hatch (from Box 12) (Offsite-box RD-559)
    - [76]-2139 | Mark Farrington (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-518)
    - 77-1875 | Dimarre (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-527)
    - 77-1877 | [Blendheim] (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-536)
    - 77-1878 | N. Ekstrom (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-525)
    - 77-1879 | Hartmann (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-525)
    - 77-1880 | Dwyer (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-525)
    - 77-1881 | Weekes (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-518)
    - 77-1882 | Beaver Dam (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-529)
    - 77-1884 | A. Ekstrom (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-518)
    - 77-1890 | Knox School all prints (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-527)
    - 77-1895 | Mark Page (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-529)
    - 77-1900 | [Cooke prop. (colyer | post enterpr.)] (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-536)
    - 77-1904 | Huntington Housing gateway gardens (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-527)
    - 77-1904 | Huntington Housing Auth. (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-529)
    - 77-1905 | Robinson (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-525)
    - 77-1905-A | Noyes FDTN Bohack Store (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-518)
    - 78-1908 | Sharretts (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-527)
    - 78-1909 | Taylor (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-525)
    - 78-1910 | Chung (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-527)
    - 78-1911 | Lloyd Harbor - police station (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-536)
    - 78-1912 | Williams (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-527)
    - 78-1913 | [Huntington] Historical Society high st. proposed additions (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-529)
    - 78-1915 | Powers (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-518)
    - 78-1916 | Browne (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-527)
    - 78-1917 | Cahn (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-515)
    - 78-1918 | United Pres [BYT.] Home (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-525)
    - 78-1919 | Dorgin (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-518)
    - 78-1921 | Dolan (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-518)
    - 78-1922 | Cowneck H. S. (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-536)
    - 78-1923 | Jaeger (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-518)
    - 78-1926 | Loomis (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-536)
    - 78-1929 | Lincoln School (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-536)
    - 78-1930 | Mallet (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-527)
    - 78-1932 | Avery (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-527)
    - 78-1933 | Elder (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-529)
    - 78-1934 | O'Neill (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-518)
    - 78-1936 | Doubleday Res. (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-536)
    - 78-1941 | Hargraves (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-536)
    - 78-1942 | Long (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-529)
    - 78-1944 | Firestone (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-518)
    - 78-[unknown job number] | Gunderman 175 W. Carver St. (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-536)
    - 79-1905-B | Mandrakis (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-528)
    - 79-1945 | Shea (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-515)
    - 79-1950 | Ames Res. (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-570)
    - 79-1951 | Townsend (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-528)
    - 79-1953 | Redmond (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-530)
    - 79-1954 | Donald Gromish [proposed] alts. Laurel Hollow NY (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-528)
    - 79-1956 | Erckert (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-530)
    - 79-1959 | Planting Fields (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-513)
    - 79-1960 | Marvin (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-513)
    - 79-1961 | Whitman Village "insulation" [illegible] (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-563)
    - 79-1963 | de Clairville (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-528)
    - 79-1963 | DeClairville (from Box 1 of 6) 79-1964 (78-1935)? Also 68-1526 (Offsite-box RD-525)
    - 79-1969 | Simon (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-513)
    - 79-1970 | Robinson (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-530)
    - 79-1971 | Arthur Dean (from Box 2 of 6) 67-1713 65-1432 (Offsite-box RD-515)
    - 79-1972 | Wardell (from Box 1 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-527)
    - 79-1973 | Boardman (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-530)
    - 80-1976 | Kerr (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-515)
    - 80-1982 | Allen (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-513)
    - 80-1983 | Trevor (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-564)
    - 80-1985 | Mulligan (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-530)
    - 80-1986 | Laurel Hollow Garage and Storage Building Additions (from Box 2 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-569)
    - 80-1986 | Memorial [Cemetery] Storage Bldg. (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-570)
    - 80-1987 | [Hafner] (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-528)
    - 80-1988-B | Barrett Treaty Corporation Huntington, NY (from Box 6 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-524)
    - 80-1989 | Burr [New] Residence (not built re-did old house instead) Owls Head (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-572)
    - 80-1990 | Gumprecht Center [Island] (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-530)
    - 80-1991 | Doukas (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-528)
    - 80-1994 | Wilkes (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-515)
    - 80-1997 | Rumbough (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-515)
    - 80-1998 | Riccardi (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-528)
    - 80-2001 | Brissenden (from Box 2 of 6) 65-1428 (Offsite-box RD-513)
    - 80-2002 | Chshman (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-528)
    - 81-2006 | Cosman (from Box 2 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-567)
    - 81-2010 | Burr [Owe's Hd. Mn.] (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-570)
    - 81-2011 | Smith (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-570)
    - 80-2012 | Lepre (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-528)
    - 81-2013 | Peters (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-515)
    - 81-2014 | Crocker - Florida (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-530)
    - 81-2019 | Richard Post (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-513)
    - 81-2020 | Eckstein (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-513)
    - 81-2021 | Sheridan (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-528)
    - 81-2024 | Mardeh (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-515)
    - 81-2025 | Tomlinson (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-571)
    - 81-2027 | Feinberg (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-513)
    - 81-2027 | Feinberg (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-528)
    - 81-2029 | Putnam (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-530)
    - 81-2030 | Francis Rue alts. and add. (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-528)
    - 81-2031 | Fonar | [oversize from various boxes] (Offsite-box RD-583)
    - 81-2032 | Henning (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-528)
    - 81-2033 | Sarney (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-513)
    - 81-2034 | O'Neill (from Box 2 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-530)
    - 81-2037 | Buckley Country Day School (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-565)
    - 81-2039 | Peter Post (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-571)
    - 82-2041 | Masciandaro (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-547)
    - 82-2042 | Cold Spring Harbor Fish Hatchery (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-562)
    - 82-2044 | Geisler (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-547)
    - 82-2046 | Mendez [illegible for two lines] (from Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-582)
    - 82-2048 | R. Brown (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-562)
    - 82-2051 | Fisher (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-562)
    - 82-2052 | Val Parker (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-580)
    - 82-2053 | Pace (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-580)
    - 82-2054 | Muma (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-580)
    - 82-2056 | Scheive (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-562)
    - 82-2057 | Putnam (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-562)
    - 82-2061 | Phillips (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-580)
    - 82-2141 | Gunther Post Lot 6 (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-565)
    - 83-2065 | Fred Williams (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-580)
    - 83-2066 | E. M. S. [illegible] (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-565)
    - 83-2066 | Episc. Mission Soc. (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-580)
    - 83-2067 | George (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-547)
    - 83-2067 | David George Laurel Hollow (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-562)
    - 83-2068 | Cunniff (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-580)
    - 83-2070 | Helping Hand Rescue (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-547)
    - 83-2070 | Helping Hand (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-580)
    - 83-2072 | Beu Taylor W. A. (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-562)
    - 83-2073 | Bunnell (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-562)
    - 83-2073 | Anne Taylor | can't find files or anything in ledger | March 1989 eep on index card lists Mrs. Bensamin Taylor | label and [illegible] by Alston | [possibly more missing] (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-562)
    - 83-2074 | Deming (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-580)
    - 83-2077 | Pres. Church of Sweet Hollow (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-580)
    - 83-2082 | Grzeszak (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-562)
    - 83-2084 | Landean Pitassy (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-547)
    - 83-2085 | Hoguet (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-547)
    - 83-2086 | Woolyerton (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-580)
    - 83-2088 | Brearley (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-562)
    - 83-2089 | Ryan (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-580)
    - 83-2091 | Corrigan (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-562)
    - 83-2092 | Abramson (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-547)
    - 83-2093 | Weir (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-562)
    - 84-2095 | Dewey (from Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-579)
    - 84-2096 | Barton (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-562)
    - 84-2097 | Sewanhaka Y. C. (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-580)
    - 84-2100 | Episcopal Mission Society (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-563)
    - 84-2100 | E. M. S. 2-2-88 (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-565)
    - 84-2101 | Becher (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-562)
    - 84-2103 | Zoller (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-547)
    - 84-2105 | Daycare Center (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-580)
    - 84-2106 | Broeders (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-562)
    - 84-2108 | Stout (from Box 3 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-562)
    - 84-2108 | Stout (from Box 2 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-568)
    - 84-2110 | Woodcock (from Box 5 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-550)
    - 84-2111 | Post (Dwgs. for Post Barns) (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-563)
    - 84-2111 | Thomas Miller Post Lot 3 (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-565)
    - [84-2111] | Post Lot 4 Murray (from unnumbered box) [84-2108] (Offsite-box RD-563)
    - 84-2111 Post Lot 5 | Horn Res. Lot 5 Post Est. S. W. James Barn (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-572)
    - 84-2111 | Cammarota Post Lot 7 (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-565)
    - 84-[unknown job number] | [illegible notes above title] Post for Andrews [illegible] August 17, 84 (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-565)
    - 85-2114 | Lubanko (from Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-579)
    - 85-2115 | Dairy Barn Stores (from Box 5 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-526)
    - 84(85)-2116 | Shepard (from Box 2 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-569)
    - 85-2118 | Irwin (from Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-582)
    - 85-2122 | Cann (Oakes) (from Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-579)
    - 85-2125 | Conigliaro, Peter (from Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-579)
    - 85-2126 | John Hans[e|o]n (from Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-579)
    - 85-2127 | Auto Body Shop (from Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-582)
    - 85-2128 | Gallatin, James (from Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-579)
    - 85-2134 | Moffat (from Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-582)
    - 85-2135 | Priscoll (from Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-579)
    - 86-2136 | Dodds and Eder (from Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-579)
    - 86-2137 | Reardon (from Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-582)
    - 86-2138 | Phillips (from Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-582)
    - 86-[2140] | [Browson] Trevor Jr. (from unnumbered box) 84-2109 and 02 79-1957 (Offsite-box RD-563)
    - 86-2142 | Nishimura [illegible] 802003 (from Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-582)
    - 86-2144 | Katzman (from Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-579)
    - 86-2145 | Davidson (from Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-582)
    - 86-2146 | Colyer (from Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-582)
    - 86-2147 | Thorne (from Box 4 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-579)